MINSU LEE

5/35 Fairfield Avenue, Addington, Christchurch, New Zealand minsuthekoiwi@gmail.com
027 844 2746

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a graduate software developer with experience in developing games using Unity and experience in multiple programming languages such as Java, Python, and JavaScript. I specialize in both VR/AR games and non-VR/AR games. I am currently developing various prototypes to learn more and more things.

WORK HISTORY

HIT Lab NZ

Christchurch, New Zealand Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

Summer Intern

Full-time summer internship

- Design and develop a mixed reality multiplayer game using Unity
- Learning a new technology/codebase
- Solving complicated problems creatively
- Testing as I develop to exterminate bugs at earlier stages
- Consulting my supervisor for improvements

Freshmax

Christchurch, New Zealand Jun 2018 - March 2020

Store Person

Casual to full-time work whilst completing my Bachelor of Science degree

- Cooperation with my team to maximise the efficiency of our performance
- Unloading and loading stock using a forklift
- A keen eye for detail to ensure accurate delivery

Bush Inn Tavern

Christchurch, New Zealand Sep 2015 - Aug 2018

Bartender

Part-time work whilst completing my Bachelor of Science degree.

- Delivering efficient and accurate service experience for three years
- Positive and meaningful customer interaction
- Handling large sums of cash
- Food preparation and drink assembly requiring high attention to detail and levels of hygiene
- Solving problems for difficult customers that require calm and logical thinking

QUALIFICATIONS

University of Canterbury

Christchurch, New Zealand 2013-2019

Bachelor of Science

Majoring in Computer Science

Mountainview High School

Timaru, New Zealand 2008-2012

NCEA Level 1-3

Subjects include:

Digital Technology, Physics, English, Calculus, Statistics

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Unity

- Developed multiple games including VR and AR games using Unity Engine.
- Developing a mixed reality multiplayer game where players will be using basic controller inputs as well as gestures and voice commands as inputs.
- Developed an archery combat defense VR game where a player has to defend a gate from enemies approaching from multiple directions.
- Developed various non-AR/VR prototypes including stealth game, mobile game and local multiplayer games
- Implementing core gameplay mechanics such as throwing objects with projectile projection, stealth takedown, and pickpocket mechanic, teleporting ability, etc.
- Ensuring that the integration process is as smooth as possible with other team members.
- Designing an in-game menu that stays consistent and fun to interact with.

Java

- 2 years of experience in Java developing apps for assignments and group projects
- Developed an app to visualize live data during America's Cup races. Following the conclusion of America's Cup, used the same software to develop a sailing game.
- In charge of decoding a stream of binary data and extracting important information, creating a UI for settings, implementing interesting features such as sharks, whirlpools and making the game touch screen compatible.

Agile software development

- Practical experience with agile software development (SCRUM) for a whole-year group project course involving the development of two projects mentioned above.
- Very familiar with roles and development life cycle involving analysis and planning, sprints, daily stand-up, review, and retrospection.

Python

 2 years of experience Python involving assignments and group projects particularly to program algorithms such as shortest-path algorithms, graph search algorithms, and sorting algorithms.

JavaScript

- 1 year of experience in JavaScript
- Developed a website for crowdfunded projects
- · Creation of a database to store user details and projects using MySQL.

• Use of Vue.js to implement user registration, sign in, searching projects by title, sorting, pledging a project and publishing your own project.

Personal skills

Problem Solving

Working at a bar has taught me how to problem solve in a logical and calm manner while dealing with difficult customers. For example, pokie machines at the bar can occasionally give out incorrect payments resulting in unhappy customers and complaints. I am able to use sound judgment to resolve problems like these and conflict under pressure. As a software developer, I thrive on overcoming challenges and am always motivated by the reward of solving a problem.

Communication

Having worked in numerous group projects and a bar environment I have developed strong verbal and written communication skills to ensure that my team members and customers are more than satisfied. I believe communication is key to working effectively in a team and building strong customer relationships.

Ability to perform under pressure

In my course involving numerous group projects, we were faced with tight deadlines. Using teamwork and efficient time management we could deliver quality products consistently and on time. Working in a bar environment during peak hours has trained me to perform well under heavy pressure.

Teamwork

I am able to work effectively in a team in group projects and at the bar. I have a relatable personality and can identify and take on the required roles in a team. For example, during a group project, we needed to ensure the project ran smoothly up to the presentation but had limited and time due to other deadlines. Having completed all of my tasks for the sprint, I was one of the few to volunteer to review everything before the presentation. This allowed us to have a successful presentation and also allowed my team members to focus on their assignments.

REFEREES

Danny Kumar

Bar Manager - Bush Inn Tavern 027 825 1919

Gurbhagat Singh Samra

Shift Manager – Freshmax 027 640 0001